Tell me how you think I'm wrong
When I say I feel so lost
Tell me why you think you're love
You erase all that it cost
Tell me why you look at me
Like I'm just a piece of dust
Tell me how you think you know
When I give away my trust
Tattoos that tell her days
Long hair flowing like a river's bend
Sweet summer Dickerson, everybody's friend
Sweet summer, wild and free
Mother of ten with a heart that can see
Birth seven stars, let her love shine through
Institutes addicts she takes
fire in her eyes but it's all rehearsed a costume disguise mean girl crown with
the jagged edge sarcasm sharp as a poison pledge she says she loves me but
daggers land unmodded degraded the sleight of hand scammer she spits while
Yeah, yeah, I'm mad. I don't think so
How are you guys I kind of thought it was a cute song, but it's like I wanted to be a sweeter song like I wanted to be like
But I love you
It was a little bit mean, okay, I'm sorry. Okay. Oh
Athens. Oh my gosh, Athens used to hear your early appearances on my show
Jamie. Jamie is in a lot of pain. Is there a student in the hospital, Jamie? I'm so sorry.
She's like going to rehab and stuff like that. Oh, but she's still the most fairest one
anywhere.
So anyway, I was at Bethesda and I was like that.
And it was like, I didn't want to like leave but it was like
She was hurting my ears, and then she didn't care. She just started yelling louder and then it was like
He started calling me mean names
So I hope I didn't call her a mean name in that song. I think it was just oh my god, but can you
Jamie
Put that
Hey, look get it out. Oh, please
Get these disgusting people out. This is like what they what?
Oh, please. Oh, we move it now. Those are my actual initials. You understand? You're my initials.
Remove the tattoo. Now, how about I remove you from the tattoo? How about a modern move,
Lady Grand Provides for President Sarah Palin. Is that Sarah Palin in the chat?
Horrifying. Okay, do you guys want to see some other clips? Oh, hold on. I have some other clips. Let's see.
Should we just shoot this? Like, let's find, I'll find a beautiful one. I'll be right back.
Mean do you guys hear me? Yeah, it was this wasn't that long ago. Oh my god. Yeah, I don't think I can put up with this guy
Oh
I want to have a butterfly. Oh my gosh. Okay. Well, we can watch some of this
Let's do this interaction right here
Okay
That's this one has a look about war right there already on the thing how like crazy is that?
Okay, let's have a look
Why is she upset? I don't understand because I shared a trip kick video that she was on
Like with that I was on suit. I think or maybe I wasn't on that particular one, but it's like
I'm also on those videos. Okay, so let's see share screen
Man, whenever that song plays, I think of that fucking one point
So I used to go to like always had that song playing over and over and over
Take him off
Future or love is the highest power
Believe in the one true power
There's a song by the death tones called pink cell phone and the very end of it is I received that song one time and it was a
It's like perfect, perfect example of like spiritual gangstocking, you know, because there's no way that something can know certain, you know, it's like, I don't know, there's, there's an element.
I've been disproving, you know certain things that I believe about like gangstocking or the people that may be involved because like
I know some of these people
We've met each other in person. We've you know, I've been around each other in social events and we are friends on Facebook, right?
You know, there's like
Facebook posts or whatever that I see of this person. I peers on my feed once in a while every now and then and I get
Yeah, and I get uh, you know, there's just these comments or posts that are like, I don't know
They feel like they're direct hits towards me, you know, you know, I totally not him, you know, it's literally like
Um, yeah, it's like they are you know, it's like things speaking to your subconscious because like you're
You know people are giving you evil eye or you know what I mean?
Cuz there's certain things that
Hint at things that no one would know unless like they had cameras and like watching you and stuff
But then like being afraid of that kind of stuff just like
Makes it to where like your paranoid, you know, and then as soon as you mention anything like that, you know
People think that you're on drugs or whatever and then or that, you know, you have mental mental disorder or something
You know, it's kind of like almost and oh, it's almost impossible to
To prove your point unless you have like actual physical
Oh, I'll leave. I'll leave. I'll leave. I'll leave. I'm sorry. No, no, don't leave. Don't leave. Stay. Stay. Stay. Stay. Please stay. No. What you do? What you're doing over there, psyche?
What you're doing, psyche?
Hello? Yeah, what's the matter? Don't why are you crying? Don't be crying. You should smile.
I mean don't do this don't do it
What
Where is it?
I'm right here
He's in the chat. I'm here. I'm here. I'm watching. I'm there. I just want to upset you. I don't want I
Don't want you to like feel the negative energy
surrounding me
I'm good energy
I'm sorry. Yeah, sorry. I'm sorry
And we use some crazy stuff man
Yeah, it's like
I think you need a moment
So a whale walks into a bar, he goes up to the, you know,
he goes up and he motions, he motions for the bartender.
Bartender says, what can I get for you?
And the whale goes, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh.
Oh, that's funny. That's funny. Thank you. That's hilarious.
Thank you.
I mean, I know so many jokes, you know, there's some inappropriate ones that I probably won't say, but man, I got to think of something like I know, I know so many
Some more jokes.
Two more jokes. Let me try to think of one. Let me see.
No, dude, a joke.
Very
Let me see.
Oh, that was this really funny joke. I heard about like, like, uh,
like eight, like 70, like 70, 79, and 78, 79. Something like that. I don't know. I can't remember.
We did high-pitched Eric go to SeaWorld to get baptized.
Oh, man.
Um, how do you, uh, um, let me see, how, uh, how do you keep a blonde from drowning?
You take your foot off her, you take your foot off of her head.
I know that wasn't super funny, but that's the first.
Let me see.
okay sir next what what did um what did what did the vibrator say to the cucumber
or what did the cucumber say to the vibrator what what are you shaking for she's gonna
Why do farts smell? So deaf people can enjoy them too.
Or here's another one. It's a church joke.
Okay, it's like, what happens to the people that fart in church?
Hello, sir.
What's the joke? What happened?
Nope. They sit in their own pew.
Now, say it all together. Say it all together real quick. Say it all again.
Say it all again.
What happens to those?
What happens to the people that fart in church?
What?
They get to sit in their own pew.
I love it.
Carl, that's funny.
If you don't leave a thing, you're a fucking human.
Motherfucker.
Yeah, that's pretty funny.
I got one for you, man.
Whatever, if you have a huge nose hole.
Oh, you're a live streamer named B.
Oh, man.
Oh, damn it.
That didn't get me.
Bitch.
That one was pretty bad.
That wasn't very imaginative.
Come on.
He said fuck that.
Oh, that's funny.
How you feel, son?
Oh, that's good.
Good to see you, big dog.
Who's that gray hair guy on the right?
Like really gray hair guy on the right. Oh, it's like they have it's like come on die your hair
That's that's I
fly
higher by flight and
man
Try again. Oh
Try again. Let me try it one more time
Um gray hair woman dye your hair lady. Is that good enough?
Come in nice come in peace
Hi Scythe here. Hi Bita. What's up girls? Hi Bita. Hi Tiger beautiful girl
He's attracted to you. Joe wants you. That's why he's like being
I want you for dinner breakfast
And I brought people here and if you know, I mean
You're in discretion that he knows
Yeah
She invites good people, okay, we have guests coming up
Never forget you're in that
What's amazing about it beta you lay out mouse well, you'll figure out
Give her a chance, you'll figure it out.
Oh, Rock is here.
Awesome.
Hello, everybody.
Hi.
Take your shirt off, Mike.
Take your shirt off, big dog.
Oh, now we have Joe trying to take fucking Psyche's shirt off.
Come on, Psyche. I was kidding.
Okay.
No, no, I'm embarrassed, isn't it?
Are you drinking another margarita? I'm so sorry.
Oh, my God.
All right, thank you.
Butterfly, this is when, like, the rules are reversed.
When, like, Psyche tried to take the guy's shirt off, now Joe did it.
Yeah, we're just having fun girl. How are you?
I was very nice. He took it all for the back going.
It was fun.
Amazing!
Hey, sorry about that guys.
Yeah, I uh,
I had a technical
difficulty.
Did you accidentally hit the
end button?
Uh,
yeah.
With what? Who are you with my with my son?
You're sitting next to the rock from he's from Afghanistan. He's a really cool guy
Wow, he's not crazy
Piece of shit
Get it your nose at all because your nose
It's not her panel, it's not her panel.
Yeah, like who who who's who's a Ravens fan nowadays anyway?
My name in Jamatria, it's like 1213 and that's the same as Baltimore Ravens is like I'm like the same as the Baltimore Ravens
Did you watch the USA Canada game they beat her ass it over time motherfuckers
If you watch the game, the hockey game.
He's so-
Hello, Syke, I'm talking to you, Syke, can you hear me?
Okay, okay, I mean, the hockey, I mean, it's like,
there weren't too many clothes for hockey.
I mean, it's like, I like the tight out,
I like the baseball and football uniform.
Hockey's like a little bit too baggy for me.
But I like the goal, I mean, he's pretty hard on us.
I mean, he's in uniform, it's more than a sport,
you're more into the uniforms.
I get it, all right, fair enough, fair enough.
Yeah.
True. Yeah, the baseball guys always look like they have tight bucks.
OK. Yeah.
You left cricket.
Tight pants, baseball.
Cricket, that's good. That's good.
I like their uniform, too.
Cricket.
Chris is a mod now.
Get a uniform, baseball.
Great.
Any like, walkie-talkie, the jockstrap under it,
it kind of like rings my bell, right?
It rings his bell. Can I tell you one thing?
Joe. I think you know, I ended her stream.
Hold on, let me say one thing.
What B ended her stream and said,
we gotta go to this guy's stream.
He's really cool.
She wasn't lying.
You're cool as fuck.
I fuck with you.
I love psyche.
And you know what, Tiger Butterfly
and neither, everybody here is cool.
I fuck with you.
Joe, like, this is your, like,
place, like, any time you want,
you can play your jokes and whatever,
but you can't get too, too far, you know?
but Joe is my bisexual buddy and I love him because he's like me and Joe we're like
he can like literally go out with me and we can pick up a dude and bring him home or he can bring
up a girl like I'm his wings and I'm in the same tent
I'm like, but like, I couldn't be just like kind of like no, like her nose is so huge.
I probably couldn't find her a man, like that's why she's lonely.
And as like, my nose is probably bigger than your nose.
You probably have a shiny one.
I'd say like, be like, you might know me, but you're the one with your hands and nobody
wants to be with you, bitch.
Joe is like the kind of guy that cannot find a hole even if he uses like three slash legs.
Yeah, I'm a favorite guy in real life.
In real life, if I've seen a woman like Bita, I would never date a woman that looks like Bita.
I'm just saying in real life.
In real life, I would never.
He wants to lick me from my...
Yeah.
Licks from my ass to my face.
Shut up.
Joe, simply you're disturbing everybody right now.
So it's like if he sees me, he was fucking like, literally, just in his pants.
Shut up, baby.
Oh man, look at this.
Shut up for a second.
Look at this.
What the hell is that?
Hi, what's your name?
Isn't that sensational, Sherry?
How about you came up right now Joe fucking Thumbly yo Peter, I'll came up when you came up
Ginger horse
And your horror
Okay, don't protect about yourself. Not you. Not you tiger. I'm talking about Josh if we love bug
I'm talking about how I know you are. I can hear you. I can hear you. I'm right here
Let's not argue anymore
Children I see the card I see the card whoever's holding that up. I want to
Joe, you're giving her a headache.
What's inside your refrigerator, bike?
Probably heads and fingers and hands.
Joe, you're driving her crazy.
I'm crazy when I look in the mirror.
I'm just like a refrigerator and tell me I'm crazy.
Bike?
I can't see.
Watch out the mud.
Feet and legs.
I don't know.
Sakey.
She called you a Joe, the hoe.
You're funny. What's going on right now?
You're even saying you're funny. You're fucking saying you're dumbass.
Let's take a butterfly.
Okay, I meant to my boyfriend right here. This is my boyfriend right here.
Is that clumsy? You always call me that when you're clumsy.
What are we doing? Call me clumsy?
It's not clumsy. That's not clumsy.
That is clumsy. That's not your friend.
No, that's not.
No, that's Chupac.
Oh
What happened is you okay, I got really worried about
She'll be okay, don't be worried. She'll be fine. Let me get over it. No, we're talking worry. Okay
Yeah, no, where is the use it's a useless the useless thing
Yeah, you don't need to worry look we're all gonna be okay
What what is that death? It's gonna be
Forehead psych no no fans, but like god damn like
No board I can run a billboard like an average
It's like an eight heads
Yeah
Damn, even a beat is getting on the action. I
Think fucking psych is sexy
And you know it's so cool. I like it. I won't say it's not serious. It's cool. It's cool.
Thank you so much.
Oh, Big Todd, I want to say I'm cuter than one of the folks, I mean I do look like him a lot, like a lot.
It's like when I first came on YouTube, Peter was like, I love you, Joe Shiffley, I love you.
I still love you guys.
She loves everybody, she's a lonely old cat lady that needs a little loving.
And if she had heard me, she might get a little bit of that lovin'.
If she had once said, look, you weren't lovin' me to come over here and get a little bit.
No, from you, whore. I don't want nothing from your fucking ginger fucking piece.
Oh, okay. Well, go get it from my twin Tommy James. He looks exactly like you.
You know, for a ginger, you know, like...
Oh, Tommy James. You're gonna bring Tommy James into this? Tommy James can rap.
Tommy James is a brother for me, you piece of shit.
You can't for not having souls you guys are a spirited bunch for sure
You want me to show you my soul you want me to see you want to see my
Are you showing your
That's me
Well Damien in the chat.
No I like Damien.
Now you said that about Kim.
You want to attack me attack me.
Why you got that Kim when she ain't here Damien?
Oh that's right cause Damien
is that little gay loser in chat that never joins panels he just stays in the chat named Damien
and attacks him which ain't here. Damien, you're one of the faggots that I've ever called.
I love you. I love you. I'm gonna say one last thing. If I ever see you in real life, Damien,
I'll break your motherfucking ass down, boy.
How would you know how would you know you could be standing right next to him on the bus like any day?
Okay, I'll take a number like way at the end
It may be to laugh and that made me laugh.
I love when I may be to laugh, I love to be to laugh.
He's just funny, I'm sorry.
He's gonna be, he just does the funniest shit ever.
He's harmless, you guys, he's harmless.
I know.
He will never porn mom, he will drop the F word
and the N word, we gotta be careful,
but yeah, I do like to do it a lot.
I mean, it's cool. I like his giggly disposition. It's great
Thank you
I know I just said Kim's not here so I shouldn't talk about her, but I know Hector's not here
I shut up about him, but I am going to I'm gonna
Shot the fuck up Vita shut the fuck up when I'm talking to site
And the reason that Hector park I could tell the guy had a little psycho in him
And now it's been kind of proven. He's a murderer and a great this and I'm only
And I don't mean rapists at the park
Allegedly, he allegedly, okay
I'm what do you meet you at the park you ugly poop? Oh
Well, you think you have the park you think I'm gonna fucking like risk fucking getting like
Whatever. Yeah, whatever.
Let's not talk anymore.
Hold on.
Can you, can you like, tell me what evil spirits are following us right now?
I just ended my words.
Can I tell you what?
Evil spirits.
Ooh, that looks good.
I'm hungry.
Yummy strawberries
I've been talking for a while about that. Nice Paul cut though, by the way
I have a bull cut. What are you talking about? Yeah, like member 1993 when bull cuts were in style
I don't even need to fuck alone Joe. I had one in my whole life.
Don't let me throw your balls head, okay?
Do it, do it, do it, motherfucker. Troll me.
Yo, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me
Can you hear me?
Here you
Unfortunately, yes, we can't hear you
Unfortunately, yes
Butterfly he jokes a lot your butterfly he's joking
Yeah
Joe right there
I
Think about ice my cousin made me think about dying when I was a lower kid
You know, you tell me how
Yeah
Dicing yeah, yeah, you know like a dice. Yeah, like die a little bit
Sir, yeah, you know live a little die a little
Are you
We're having fun guys
Really like some he just said
You know
I love you beat up
I'm gonna show my fighter butterfly. He'll go on you slowly
No
I'm like a bird
It's Natalie Portado. We weren't talking about you. That's not me for time. I'm like a bird. I'm like a bird
Run away, train, never travel back
One way, another one way to die
Feels like I never get in somewhere outside
And if I saw Joe, I would f**king take him by the head, and f**king put him out of his penis, because he's a dick, and he's not bad dick.
Don't ever talk about psyche.
We're saving psyche to the end.
You're gonna need to be thrown under the train.
Oh, he's gonna play the guitar. Hold on.
He plays the instrument.
Oh!
Alright, okay, we're gonna play it.
Make it full screen. Make it full screen.
Wait.
Stop.
Shut up, Peter.
Yeah, he's got a, he's got that one song, yeah, he's got a, he's got a, he's got that one song.
I don't know your name, I never met you on live panels, but that was awesome.
That was really cool.
My boyfriend.
Aw, yeah.
That was nice to meet your boyfriend.
Where did that come from?
I thought I was your boyfriend.
It's like, wow, that's really rude.
I hope.
Yeah.
Wow.
Oh snap.
Cheers, cheers.
What are you drinking?
Oh, Rita.
God, you are gay, Rita's beer.
Christ's like, no offense, but you are fucking gay.
Like really, is that really a beer?
How would you know if you didn't try this?
How did you know, Joe, you did it?
You tried it, Joe?
He knows a beer. He didn't mean to see the whole label.
I would ever...
Maybe I'm bisexual or bi or whatever it tastes like.
He didn't just have to dye that facial hair a little bit.
Them gray hair is not.
Come on, old man.
He's looking like an old man over there.
He looks fucking hot. He looks like a model.
He looks like a better-looking,
fucking blogger.
I don't dye my hair.
actually he does actually kind of look like he looks like a way better than
oh look at him put his hair back in here well Joe you demand big dough
up guys
You guys
Took the I took the liberty of pulling rolling some dice for you guys
But we would like that though
Well
A couple of days in there, okay
Joe could be 66.
What's our left first beat?
I'm in your mind.
Psyche, Psyche, Psyche, you'll be 55, Psyche, you'll be 55.
Let me see
No cap no cap
All right, so did I get 44 or 66?
I only got my small one.
Shut up, four.
Let's look at our burdens.
How about we look at what's burdening us?
Yeah?
So.
Little eavesdrop in here. This is what's burdening us. All right
Psych psych what's burning you is success success is burdening you right now
All right, there's public public recognition. That's burdening you right now. That's for psych
Okay, all right, let's what's burdening you right now is not moving quick enough
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
You could bring a horse to water, but you can't make him drink
What's burdening you is this page of pentacles
Yeah, what's burdening you is this person that's trying to give you something or offer you something.
So someone offering you something is burdening you.
That's probably Joe here.
This could be Joe.
I don't even care that much about Joe to even think about him.
He says, will you bury me?
Let's clarify that. Oh look at that look and you're not putting any effort towards this proposal. So that's why you're
Hey now, okay, it's us burdening us right now
I'm not gonna pull for myself because I'm not gonna let all y'all into my business
No, we want it. Let's see that. I
Didn't really myself so yeah
you know what i like about you betha that you say you never date me like betha i wouldn't date you
any day of the fucking week you understand me do you hear what i'm saying you betha yeah of course
i wouldn't touch you with a fucking 25 in school well i'm so glad the feeling in this school oh my god
look at that card look at that card oh we got the same one as me outside down card but it's a man
That's it's the same one you got like mine
I did I totally did
Tell us like our life story at least shuffle the fucking guards a little bit
Can I three minutes these are your minutes I want to play yeah, yeah, yes
Here we go.
I'm sorry.
I have a bag.
No, could be said meow.
He's unknown challenger who comes from behind.
I don't mean to have a magical voice.
Oh my God.
Really psyched.
The song has a nice drop.
I like the drop.
Katy Perry?
The Egyptian did not like this one.
you and pick you up just like a man but I'd probably wear these costumes like
a parody this looks like a stage at birding man
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
That was, that was horrifying what I just saw.
Okay.
Who is that?
You ready for?
Are you ready for?
That's great psyche little comic really so order of operations order of operations
that's what I got from that
Order of operations. You know, sometimes my order of operations. Yeah, sometimes my order of operations gets all fucked up.
Do you think that order of operations is right?
I don't think he's a nice person I think I think I think he's I think I think he's a I think he's a great person
meaning like a good human I don't know nice there's nice I don't like that word it's like nice
say nice like this bully probably said nice like oh it rhymes in my high school
bully but it's like
Let me talk when you were in high school second. They dumped you upside down and gave you a swirly
They've dumped your fucking head into the urinal
I love sake. I fuck with sake. I'm just saying if you got done to do the fucking tool is don't fucking bring it on me
Geez
My bisexual
Of course, I've been telling you all night
Joey's might the guy that I would hang out with the boring we would
Yeah, Joe is definitely my bisexual buddy.
I'm bi-neural. No, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I
I'm a big homo. I don't know. Yeah, me too. Me too. Big A-fag.
It was not when Pabble was bad. It was really the real Pabble.
Music sounds like Jamie Rose.
I love you, Pabble.
Jamie Rose's voice. She's the same tone as Jamie Rose.
He's like Jamie Rose.
I like Jamie.
You you basically
Basically the same boys
Bisexual for years
I mean, you know what?
Biceps for me. It's not like women too, and I'd say right now
Rather make out with fucking pebbles to you
It's a Friday night, it's my party night of the week, so it's gonna be a chaotic show, but I'll be quiet, guys.
I can't hold that noise.
Stop burning Joe on like that.
That's burning me on.
That's my blood hole.
That's my blood hole dripping.
The blood hole is mating right now.
It's kind of a blood hole dripping.
Yeah.
The blood hole dripping when my cock is gone.
Why am I hearing ICP in my head right now?
What is up with that?
I don't know, but the only good song they have is, I don't even know one good song.
They don't have one good song, but they're cool though, they don't have one.
I
Hey, ICP doesn't suck when it's 2002 and you're like 12 years old
Do you guys remember that, uh, drink Zima? Was it Zima? That was like clear beer?
Say it's 7up, clear beer, yeah.
It's a clear beer.
They have cool commercials.
I like their commercials. Their commercials are cool.
Yeah, so Susanna, you would say earlier, like, my challenge is public recognition because
the more popular I get, the more famous I get, the more people hate me, the more people
love me at the same time.
It's a blessing and a curse.
I love that. I hate you. I love that. I love you. I don't need no one above you.
You're famous like all the more famous I got.
please
Like the new upcoming kind all over the place
Don't think you could keep treating a woman bad
I'm doing I'm doing fine. I'm doing fine. I'm doing fine. I'm taking off really fast
It's five o'clock in the morning
Subscribers in six months
That's not bad.
Really good.
You know what I think it is?
Your grizzled chin, your grizzled facial hair and chin.
That's what it's got.
That good looks.
That's what it is like.
Your good looks is attracting all the viewers.
Well, those eyes are actually Charles Manson's eyes.
So tapping on more of the grizzled hair.
I've ever asked to see Joe's refrigerator and he will never show it's either ever
I've known him for a long time he will not show us in the freezer Joe Joe freezer
No, it doesn't show freezer.
Freezer, welcome to your freezer.
Not in your fridge, welcome to the freezer.
Oh my god
You always let me on your panel. I'll fuck with you. You always let me come up on your panel. I appreciate that
I know she's doing okay. I like her. She always let me come. Thank you, Bita
What do you mean?
Well, you let me out. You let me up on your panel, you fucking retard.
I'm trying to give you a compliment, you fucking moron.
You're not listening to me.
She just, she just flips her hair.
Oi, she's cussing you out.
You're trying to fucking tell her I like Jordan your panel.
She cussed me down.
I don't want to come back down from this club.
It's taking me all this time to find out what I need.
Trace people.
I adore people.
It's taking me all this time.
Jim Kitty.
Yeah.
I'm making the chat
It's like it's impossible to have like a normal terror show
Cuz then it's like eventually they'll find like my crazy stream
Wow, you got a nice hand, man.
I'd like to give you a high five.
That looks like Joe Shiffley's face.
Oh my goodness.
You want to do it, Beto?
Didn't they want to do it?
You want to fucking do it?
That's the way you want to go.
I was walking around outside, barefoot, you don't want to see my feet right now, you're so dirty.
You don't want to show your face, you're embarrassed of your face.
I'm showing it many times, that's how you know what I look like.
You don't show your camera for a reason, because you're embarrassed of your own face.
You don't know what I look like and you're going to keep it mysterious, but you see me many times, that's why you lick my ass.
I
Wow you believe that stuff?
It's funny. Oh, hello, is it going there? Oh, okay. Wow
So fun
No, it's funny that you don't like actually thought I called her and I did it
I'm gonna call someone called her it's like you know the old Chinese restaurant joke where you like call a Chinese restaurant
But then it's like a call another Chinese restaurant. You swim together. They're like, who'd you call their attorney to each other orders?
It's all confusion, but
Hold on
I'll put my link up anyway this hear me all right my mic
Here's my link
And you know what's to come up. I know it's all in good fun too. I mean, I don't I don't have anything against Vita
I think they're like
Playing with me my dumb playing reruns. Have you ever seen it before because it's not a rerun
It's the first time you've seen that
It's called a classic actually
Oh gosh, I'm a little bit hot outside.
I think I'm gonna put my sandals on and put a stupid coat on.
All right, we're out.
And so it's real exciting.
Oh my God.
Okay.
Whoa.
It's good time.
Dry it on the way home, yeah, almost all of it.
Guys, you see how cool I have a new studio I put in there.
There's like, you know,
see there's a person back there, I think.
Here.
She's like she might like a share a little bit. No, I think there's me
Anyway, so I walked through to get the cigars and McDonald's
Yeah, but you see how happy I was I was like kind of happy there because I was happy. I was like just so drunk. I
Was in a good mood
But I remember I started to like just feel like under attack by the people like they were sending these passive aggressive things
Like you kind of saw thinking you can see the one even when I'm out there
So it's like makes me think it's like my this meeting paranoid, but I don't think it is
I think it's like kind of like they
and I let me know what they're talking about.
That's the blemintal stuff.
I learned a lot about it from the Russian people.
Why don't you read this panel?
Because she was starting to call me just names
and like, just was not being reasonable with conversation
and I was being reasonable and I didn't want to start yelling.
And so I just was like, you know what?
I'll just go play the, play some of her on my panels.
She accused me of all this stuff.
Like, oh yeah, but I did want to play something
a whole lot more soon.
Do you guys want to hear one more thing?
Let's try this.
So this is the, I guess they call it the industry, they call this the B side.
This is the B side.
I'm not going to play, oh.
Probably not going to play this song too much.
Let's see.
Hey Lola. Let's see if this works.
I might need a phone.
Where's my, whatever it is.
It's hot
Costume disguise
Mean girl crown with a jagged edge
Sarcasm sharp as a poison
She says she loves me but dad
Yo
Hello, do you hear me God God easier? Hello? Hello?
Hello I
Can hear you now yeah, okay
Look, I see my new window. Okay, I finally got a window put in my apartment. You see outside. Isn't it?
Well, you see and what is that mega man? It's all purple. It's like a it's like a magical purple city
You could like go through it's like a portal
Yeah, well, I tried before and I just hit my head on the wall, but I'm gonna try again later
Right now I want to see
I'm not gonna do it. I don't want to break anything. I don't want to break anything. It's very new. It's very new
What's going on man? He's killing
I'm doing good. Like, you know, but that wasn't like supposed to be like a diss track or whatever to be that
I was like I was like supposed to be like a sweet song like
But I still love her, but I forgot to say I still love you and so it kind of came out of this song
But you know what? I think it's kind of a cute song. So do you hear the song or no?
No, I just came in literally just now. Okay. Well, I'm not gonna play again right now, but I'll play it later
But how would you guys like it?
Because being is like saying oh, it's like a war and something like that
And I was like, what do you mean a war is like why would it be war?
It's like you have a war was like because she's talking about the art of war and I thought and I know all about like these like
read these 48 Laws of Power, the Art of Seduction.
It's too much.
Of course it's going to be beat as top of her list too.
Art of War, I mean, everything is like a 600-year-old Chinese
book.
It's interesting, but it really does not have that many
things you could use today.
It's basically like, you know, it has some good information,
like hide in the shadows, and you're far of making them
think.
You're near when you're near me. Why don't you write her a letter write a really heartfelt letter. Yeah
That's a fire gift
No, no, if you send it to her that's more from the heart
She doesn't want a gift. I mean if I the gift is like my like me. I'm like, I'm not or she's a gift
The gift is the gift is like the people not that like the you know, my personal thing the gift is like the friendship the gift is like
Just like the love it's like but not
But it's a kind of like, you know a booby prize or I don't know
Think it's like you got you understand that there's a million people in the world with a million different feelings
All right, not everybody's the same and nobody wants to be treated the same some people want special treatment
Some people want to be fucking yeah
We deserve special treatment guys. We do we deserve it. Well, I I get it. I mean, I
We demand it exactly we have to demand it. I really don't I'm like Rodney danger feel kind of big
But you know what, you know, I hope you do get it and as you deserve respect and like a lot like, you know
Maybe I don't but it's like
You know everybody does yeah, I mean I deserve like she basically been digged in he that's all I'm wanting
It's like respect is like a hole. Oh, that'd be like really cool
But it's like as long as I've treated like you know, not like a farm animal
You get what you give in life if you give it
But if I give sweet sweet milk better than flirty diamonds milk
And people love it. I don't know what's going on between you and beta, but it's not working whatever you're trying to do
It's not working. So maybe I'm not trying to do anything. Do you want me to play back?
You're trying to be friends with it. You're trying to be friends, right?
No because the ghost called me and said hey, they're just talking all this shit about you
And I was already there earlier. I heard him talking
I was like, okay
He's like please come on panel cuz he didn't know what to say
I guess he's just trying to get the drama going so I went on panel and then she like sort of calling me a scam artist and
Like, you know just being really mean and so I was like hey
You know what? I'm just gonna go to my own show and like play some old video clips
So that's why you know how many young people talk shit about me on a daily basis on here
I can't talk shit about me. Most people say good things. At least I hear bells and good things. I just hear all negative about me. I don't hear anything good. I don't hear anything good. I don't hear anything good. I don't hear anything good. I don't hear anything good. I don't hear anything good. I don't hear anything good. I don't hear anything good. I don't hear anything good. I don't hear anything good. I don't hear anything good. I don't hear anything good. I don't hear anything good. I don't hear anything good. I don't hear anything good. I don't hear anything good. I don't hear anything good. I don't hear anything good. I don't hear anything good. I don't hear anything good. I don't hear anything good. I don't hear anything good. I don't hear anything good. I don't hear anything good. I don't hear anything good. I don't hear anything good. I don't hear anything good. I don't
Well, especially I'm a cap report so that's right in the house public opinion, but I have my Lilith there
And so it's like Lilith is like the biggest outcast so it's like I knew I'd be outcast but I
Have a magnetism with the Scorpio
There's a big gift that overshadows the curse that came with it, but it was a big curse
You think it was a gift to you think thank you much. I'm
What negativity from your life just cut out all negativity you'll be fine
I don't know but you can't cut out of the negativity because it's part of life too
It's like you can't just like be like oh then embrace your course
Embrace the negativity then to the opposite. I don't want to know. Oh, see you want to kick in you want to eat it, too
Then there's no warning for me. I want to transform it. I would be treated like a human being
Someone's like, oh, he has a mouth open like sirex. Look at him chew like chew like a
You know a pig dude, dude, you're hungry. What do you what do you expect you got your camera on everybody's watching you?
What do you everybody's gonna be a critic? Well, look at my window look at the window
What is that this Mega Man?
Mega Man
Guy look very close. I'll very close the bottom. Oh
Shit that's Orion it's with another girl
Oh my god
There's one behind the curtain right I can't see
Hold on, I guess I don't like it
Orion
That's J-One
Oh my god
I think that's the grandmother from Puckie Brewster
I'm not sure, hold on one second
This is Johnson, her name was
Hold on one second
Let's see, visual
Let's have a...
This is some old art of mine
Can't really see it that well
Okay, here's more art. That's cool. If you could put that on the whole wall like that, that'd be awesome. I
Know I got to get some more of this green screen. It's like because I mean it's it is not like I
Could like put it sideways and we get like up there, but it's like it'd be hard to like
Use like a ladder and I might probably fall and so like that so I need to like
Have somebody handy help me put up the rest of the thing was like how cool it can look if I have the whole like wall like that
I can put up any
Thank you. You can go anywhere. You could be anywhere in the world right now
Yeah, I can be in a space
You could go to like fucking Mars. You can go to space. I don't want to go to Mars. I want to be on earth
Where you want to be I'm you can just be I think we are we already really I think we already ruined Mars
Isn't it like I'll turn red and it's like all in have uninhabitable now. You know speak speaking of Mars, dude
Remember we were talking about this asteroid
It's full of fucking carbon dioxide right carbon dioxide
So if it crashes go ahead eat your fucking Big Mac if it crashes into Mars, right?
It could fucking activate the thermo fucking
Geothermal energies that are in the core of Mars, and it could actually fucking create like an atmosphere on Mars. You know I'm saying
With all that carbon dioxide
Then all this fucking all these plants will start growing. It'll be like a garden of Eden
Because maybe but maybe I don't know I think we have to do like a greenhouse kind of thing
We need we need like a green house yes
Well, I mean it's all greenhouse effect though. I don't want to talk about some of the stuff
That political which we talk about Mars
I don't yeah, okay, but I want to talk about the environmental stuff, but yeah, okay Mars with my is Mars real
I think it's like maybe like in a desert in the in like Arizona or something like that was pepperoni in the sky
It's just a piece of pepperoni. They just drive around a golf cart in the in the Mojave desert and you know put some put it under like
You know 1978, you know film and then it's like, you know, oh my gosh look
I don't know. Why do you even go to Mars in the first place?
Do you even want to go there?
Yeah, we should go there. Yeah, we could send all the episodes.
I don't want to go there.
Well, you know it's forcing you to go.
No, it's forcing you.
You are going to go there.
No, but you know, in South Florida they have an episode where they go to Mars
and it's like, but then it's like, and carbon really wants to go,
but it turns out like, the women are like...
Locking the men underground and like milking them for their seamen and their jokes
Yeah, cuz they don't have either yeah, well they do they will come on
Let's just say Lisa Lampinelli does not write her own material
She died she did oh no, so yeah, I think she's dead
You know how she died
She felt this down in a bush. No
She thought of reflection
Goddy she's still alive. She does. Yeah, but she doesn't think she is let me look it up. Hold on. Okay. She's alive probably I don't think she died I
Feel her spirit still with us
And in that human meat soup
Oh talking about me say that I'm selfish
I
selfish
How am I so I mean just like compared to what we're doing?
But I like I love myself
My narcissist. Oh, she's a lot fucking bitch. She's alive. You know Venus says she's talking about me and she says I'm selfish
What do you think Goddy?
Well, that's somebody else saying it if you're here for yourself, that's different
But that's somebody else I believe she said that she said I mean I heard her say worst things when I was there
She's called me a scammer anything like that, buddy
Hey, people say things man. I don't believe everything. That's my friend. That's my friend and it's like and then
She has the elder one has a picture of like the north like hanging in a weird
Position and then like and then somebody else
Her friend Oliver
They just have like a little laugh over like, you know biscuits and whatever over like, you know
He has a picture like he put through AI of me that makes it makes me look like
Monster I was showing your I was showing your high school photo last night on a summer spell
Did you see it?
Are we doing that? How'd you why did you save my high school photo? You are you the one?
Yeah, you want to see it? Hold on. Are you the one that saved it and you and message me?
You know, I've been getting calls a tip like yeah, we can see it. Do not hope you did not mess with it
I was a very good-looking person back then
Hello
Yeah, this is it
That's not me, I'm kicking you off, I'm kicking you off, I'm kicking you off, I'm kicking you off, I'm kicking you off, I'm kicking you off, I'm kicking you off, I'm kicking you off, I'm kicking you off, I'm kicking you off, I'm kicking you off, I'm kicking you off, I'm kicking you off, I'm kicking you off, I'm kicking you off, I'm kicking you off, I'm kicking you off, I'm kicking you off, I'm kicking you off, I'm kicking you off, I'm kicking you off, I'm kicking you off, I'm kicking you off, I'm kicking you off, I'm kicking you off, I'm kicking you off, I'm kicking you off, I'm kicking you off, I'm kicking you off, I'm kicking you off, I'm kicking you off, I'm kicking you off, I'm kicking you off, I'm kicking you off, I'm kicking you off, I'm kicking you off, I'm
Okay, I had a worse photo than that 8th grade, okay, but I
High school photos were pretty good. Not my favorite
It was kind of funny. Well, you know make sure you go, you know, see when he does stand up it
Oh, we can't stand if he's in a wheelchair. I'm so sorry. That was a really stupid. Okay. That's hard. That was bad
I'm sorry. You can't you can't he's not I don't even think he's in a wheelchair
He's making him off. He's also and the name got to I bet it's fine. I like I love him
Put it into marbles and magic. Unfortunately, marbles and magic, you know, they went looking
for some pussy and, you know, they went out for milk and they never came back. But you
know what? I believe they found the pussy, and I believe that they're happy and helped
because this neighborhood is very good about taking in cats. We don't even have a shelter
here because there's no need for one people to just take in all the cats. A lot of, like,
older women, you know, ladies here that like cats, you know.
But I like dogs too, there's dogs all over this neighborhood.
And that's what happened to poor Marbles of Magic, you know, well actually Marbles was
back for like a month and then he left again, but that's what cats do sometimes, you know,
they have freedom to go where they please, they're not least shadowy, you know, put a
like a shock collar on them or something, I can't, you know, the ones that want to be
here are here, but there's no, oh there's tricks of sleeping over there, I think it's
I look like I'm about to cry me
Tommy James well didn't tell me James. I don't want to say anything bad about him
He just he looked like he was 20 years older over the night
He looked like I'm like like
Yeah, like Dom de la Huiz before he died
or like that
Who's the Star Wars? Who's the guy that directed Star Wars George Lucas? Oh, excuse me
Let's play a nice song. Let's like forget about this. It's like bad things and let's play a happy song.
Let me see.
I guess so
Panels get wild like Friday night, cards on fire, drama ignites, crystals flying, she's taking flight
Mixing costume, eyes are red, bong in hand and nothing said
Till he drops a quote, half baked and weird, then laughs like a wizard with a twisted beard
This ain't your grandma's terrorist show, where the cards fall fast and the weirdness flows
We stir the pot, we break the mold, its psyche awakens uncontrolled
Mildos driving CB Blair in truck stop wisdom always there and he calls in loud kicks up
the mess starts a feud in the comments non-stop stress
Sponky jumps in with a wink and a bun sharp like tarot sweet like sun
rolls her eyes sips her tea brings the heat with sarcasm glee
Here, with a smirk so sly, draws Paige's face with a sparkle eye.
Flirts like crazy, Paige just grins.
She rolls the dice and the chaos begins.
Crystal buzzes from 30,000 feet.
Dropping hot takes, can't be beat.
One minute's in, next minute war.
Drops a truth bomb, then ask for more.
Buckle up, it's a tarot ride.
Where the drunk, the bold, and the cursed collide.
From docks and drama to bong hit scenes.
Welcome back to Psyche Awakens, where the cards are sharp and the panels get cut.
Let's talk about who didn't survive the vibe.
You ghostly face.
And addicts, they got kicked off the panel, now they haunt the stream.
Trying to flex with no talent, just a boot and a scream.
You acting like stars, but you barely gleam.
Now you're stuck in the chat like a failed meme.
From MC Nemesis, boy, sit down quick, getting loud fine.
But stop saying that, you drop bars with no rhythm or cringe than raw.
I had to boot you out.
flash me you bro no thanks your balls got less views than my tarot ranks this
ain't omegle this is mystic art you showed up nasty and left with a fart
chow Q gets green when my numbers climb jealousy's a color that don't match
your sign trying to drag me down with that weak debate but your mic cuts out
when I levitate have a bugger try to clone me bleached in all but your
styles knock off like a bathroom stall my panels
I'm making earthquakes Duke sick puffing dull like a two-hour nap calling yourself incel now
You just yeah, no sauce. No spice. No vibe. No thrill your background noise with an ego to fill how mr.
Big pipes more like mr. Mid you talk a lot
Crowd shows me why you gas your mic with mediocrity.
This panel's protected, the vibe is tight.
If you show up wild, you're gone by night.
Tarot cards cut, don't test the flame.
Get booted fast, we remember your name.
Naked, they got kicked off the panel,
now they haunt the stream.
Try to flex with no talent, just a boot in the screen.
Now they rage in the comments, petty and mean,
but I'm still live, still lit, still clean.
Rest in pieces, panel ghosts.
Next time, bring something real to the table.
and pieces panel ghost next time bring something real to the table till then
Veronica leave me alone. I had 30 people in the chat obviously it's not like
scaring everybody away. If you'd like to hire me to do some AI for you, I'd be happy to.
No actually yeah it is quite expensive to do so. I mean not me it's like you know
the credit system they have. Oh chat CPT gives instruction like oh my gosh it's
No, it's chatting. That's because that everyone's hate watching like usual. I have a bunch of hate watchers
I'm in a spaceship right now. You see how it's the outer space right there and
They just oh, they're just pretending if it's constantly hard enough that window might break out, but you know what that windows never break out
Very very very strong. I mean you're chatting you're chatting with me you get one-on-one. How lucky are you tonight?
Well, 31 to one
You know
I'm chatting. But anyway, yeah I did get my power chat working and I don't know if like
some people just prefer to use that one. I mean I'll put it up and everything, but you
don't have to tell me to go look at it right now because it's not that compatible with StreamYard,
but it can work on it.
I might get the updated thing, so I'm absolutely sure.
I don't think I can play music, anyway.
OK, um, power chat page.
OK, so I'm there.
It's like, yo, it gets me.
I'll put this on my iPad.
Oh, excuse me, I'll put this on my link page too, but if you guys are interested, there we go.
And I'll read your message on the chat. I'm going to have to pin that if I can.
No one's coming up. Well, here you go.
she has a better setup with music and stuff. I just can't risk people sending n-word songs and stuff.
You know, it's like, you know, I watched one of these old episodes and like somebody came in
porn bombing the n-word saying, that's a horrible song. The house next door to me has been sold,
and it's like a racist song, and then everyone was like, oh, I have the first time he's a legend.
What is this? The KKK rally? Why are people so interested in all these racist, terrible things?
I mean, I don't like it. Anyway, I do want to say thank you to the
donors on the power chat, how they've received those donations. Thank you so much. I appreciate that so much.
I don't know where everyone is today. Probably at Bita's. I think Bita's yelling about me.
But to prove there's no heart feelings, here's another song.
You said right a funny cute loving song about be tough. She is the host of beat is kitty
She is a beautiful Persian woman. She is so funny. She has a hysterical laugh
She is so loyal and true. I have a bkg tattoo her cats are Mickey and Mohammed
I will glove her always. Thank you be tough
Sure, here's a funny, cute and loving song about Bita
The host of Be Ask Kitties with a mix of sweetness laughter and purring kitties
Think acoustic ukulele or soft indie pop vibe
Thank you, Bita
You're a Persian queen on screen with cats. You're living the dream Mickey and Muhammad at your side
You laugh so loud the stars collide your host beat as kiddies
It's a wild ride with eyeliner sharp and a heart so wide you tell the truth you never lie even when your cats knock down the
Wi-Fi
Thank you
This is the last week of the year in the world.
I, I love you.
And I do hate you.
Hamid steals your shoe
She's got sass and she's got style and she can make a troll cry in a while with just one wink and that Persian grace
And a kitty filter on her face
Pizza's heart is full of gold. She'll keep you warm when the world is cold and when she laughs
Oh man, you'll see it's like a rainbow with extra glee
It's knocking down stuff with his feet but Vita just giggles and sings along like she's starring in
So here's my song, it's cheesy but true
Written with cat hair and love for you
Beat eyes, kitties, forever will be
A show of love and cats
And beat up and knee-
You said, right, a funny, cute
L-
Persian functions, petty, poetic justice
Satan came through with a tray and a smirk
Talking bout biscuits like she did the work
But baby, those scones were drier than Tehran
Where's the honey sauce, girl, it's gone
You say you're the queen of the big off crew
But your butter slipped out like it's dodging you
I brought saffron, cardamom, rosewater drizzle
I'm the mountain sun, voice of the dawn
Where the climbs begun, words like pillars
Fire in my hands, I build the temple on shifting sands
And a freedom flame
I love in secret
Yet I love the same
A hidden fire
A mystic song
A banner that's kept it tried
I was a mud in the land of tarot dreams
I'm a ranch like a sword in the stream
I'm a Leviathan, demon, queen, divine
Read the cards, stole my soul and crossed the line
Without you, I'm stuck in hell.
I was fake, Elon, I was Nick Cage too.
Wrote in all caps, I'd steal the moon for you.
refresh your channel just to see your face in 1080p.
We could have been Tarot Talk royalty.
It's for my name.
Well?
Baccarat.
Oh, come on, no.
No, no.
I think it's my coping mechanism, this music.
You know what?
I'm gonna go with it. I'm just gonna go with it. No
in slurring words starting up a scene talking all that trash then she flips
rage queen mad at me girl please this show runs on caffeine socks twisted
laughing loud whiskey in his veins slurge flying left and right we cut the
feed no shame but the chats on fire can't tame this flame this ain't your
mama's podcast this a runaway welcome to the madness buckle up
But she ain't got time for a dude like that Diamond flirting hard let the girls react it's a freak show party
No filter all facts. Yo, yo Michael drops a line gong not tonight
Alex tried to joke boom sent into the night panel look inside way
Someone's got a fight producers on mute praying this don't spike
Diamonds feeling spicy shirts slipping down low oops. She says with a wink. That's the whole shit
But still cracking jokes slurred out wisdom with a bourbon soap glow no rules just rolls
We pretend to play one hand on the mute of the letting this spray. It's a circus a riot a beautiful mess
One wrong word and we're trending in the welcome to the madness buckle up tight boops flashing on camshaft losing their mind
But she ain't got time for a dude like that diamond flirting hard let the girls react
It's a freak show party. No filter all facts
The lights out one more round beat is on the line. He is on the line
It goes from a bottle of wine cry we crash rewind same time next week, you know the vibe welcome to the man
Welcome to the man
Enjoy the ride
Welcome to the madness
I had
Enjoy the ride
Welcome to the madness
Buckle up tight
Boops flashing on cam
Chat losing, losing their minds
Losing their minds
I'm a loserator
You're a loserator
But we do it every night and you're a liar
Welcome to the mad
How are we doing guys? Are we sleeping? Okay.
Well, I'll take off.
It's my lab. Um, Vanguard.
Or whoever wants to know.
I want to talk to Vanguard, please.
Not Vita.
Vita's a douchebag.
Oh, here he is.
Hello, Governor!
Hello, there fucking soggy fucking fella.
You alright, mate?
Hi, how are you, mate? I'm alright.
Hold on, let me take the banner down.
How are you? The show looks a little bit better though, hold on, let me get the scanner off too.
Hey Vangar, I didn't realize you'd been with this show for so long. You were here for like six months ago, weren't you?
I wouldn't say that. I've been on a five-month-old show and you were on it last night.
We're talking to an old friend already.
Are you sure that was me? Are you sure that was me?
Look yourself anywhere. I'm not here to cause trouble. I'm here to have a laugh and say
Um, I know I've known Alexander me is quite a few years and used to crack on I'm not here to discuss that
I'm here to talk about everything and anything or follow what?
But I'm gonna say if you don't have anything nice to say don't say anything at all, but
I'm not gonna hear cause trouble mate
I've known a mate I was on panel with you and Alexander
a month or so ago
Yeah, and she knows Jimmy Riz or she knows me from them dears. Come on. Okay. Well, I mean
I'll judge people about or through is basically my relationship with them. I try to like, you know, not
Bring in like everybody else
Only problem I've had with you when I'm on a weekend when I've had a drink is
You'll exhaust the panel and you know when when some people leave you just take everybody off the panel
That's the only thing negative. Well, I get tired too and I get tired too and then and then people are not like sometimes
You know, I need to like eat and stuff like that if I'm like if I'm like, you know wanting for something
And it's like I'm like sitting up here trying to like
I like it. Oh
Do you know what I like the short you release in a very quick succession like shooting a gun like you know
I know what I'm about that gun and you really so many shorts of everybody
That's been a belly and I think that's what I'm not trying to like I'm not kind of culpable out or anything
I'm just putting up the clips that come out and what I think are interesting
I mean I had a 10 hour video or 11 hours and it came up with 600 clips out of it that I had to choose from
I mean that's like a lot to choose from right? I want to put up like 10 out of the 600 so that's like you know
very still think it's
Hello thing thing thing. That's what?
Hello. Oh no don't you think that is his name is thing that is
What do you think about the controversy? Have you seen the controversy that's going on the guy?
I don't know. He's talking to me so yeah. Yeah. Um, what's going on? I?
I chatted earlier when I got up. I was like, what's going on?
I just got up and it seems like there's a war. I don't really know what's going on.
Well war like because I mean she was using the words like war and like you know
She was talking about the art of war and like blow-blah and they're talking about being super like you know
Secret about whatever they're talking about but the same talking about the same exact stuff in the same event like a secret little tone
it's like a very like a
Kind of narcissism that's called like superhero complex or something. I don't know how many of you read some sue before
Yes, I have read art of war, but it's like
Don't like sit there setting and like it's like my like you know made it for life
I just like you know read it and it's like oh interesting
I had well I didn't mean to mention war like as an actual war. I just meant I woke up and there's like a battle going on
I didn't know what the heck's going on
Well, I mean it's like you know the thing about war is like you know
Both sides have to like, you know, no, it's like or else it's something called a silent war
Which is like actually what was predicted and
Behold the pale horse. Did something trigger this again today or is?
Just to continue. Yeah. Well, I went I went over the I mean it triggered me because I was well
I did trigger but I went over there just to like listen and it's like I was being talked about the whole day and then
Like but I was like not calling in then ghost called me and he's like or he like texted me like say hey
They're talking a lot of shit about you. He's like you come up on panel
And I would hope that he could just like you handle it
But he didn't know what to say really I guess and so I went up there and just like talks a few minutes
She started calling me names and I just left and started my own life. So
You know, she's not being very nice with how she's treating me. She's being very slanderous, actually.
And she's saying I'm being slanderous. We're just showing her, actually her clips, right?
I don't exactly get it. It's a little crazy to me. It's...
I don't know what to say. I just don't like you both and I wish you guys weren't fighting but
Because I'm not privy to the latest gossip
Yeah, I'm not here to try and smooth things over or talk for anybody in particular
I really just came up to check on you psych see how you're doing. Oh, I'm fine
I'm absolutely fine. It's just you know, I'm having like a little bit of a stress more stressful time now
Yeah, you know, it's like, you know, it's a kind of trickle down from other areas of my life
And it's like, you know, it's just like everything kind of like
Or it's like it'd be nice to have like, you know people
You know like hurt like, you know me supportive of me right now instead of like trying to like, you know hurt me and like
It's like for no reason. I wasn't even like being mean yesterday. I was being playful and it's like what because I have her old clip
song
Well, she said what she said in those old clips and stuff like that and it's like wait
It's like even if you you're not the same person those clips
So obviously like no one really no one really cares in the first place about. Oh, it's not a big deal
Plus it was just like two minutes of it. I turned it off
Then she started saying my that beat his biscuit song was like talking about her family
It's there's nothing I just played it does not talk about any of that just
That's because it's a little bit dry.
Well, since you know that she's sensitive about that,
unless you're trying to get under her skin, maybe, just.
But that's the thing.
That was something I was like, can you stop saying the word
biscuit, because they wouldn't stop saying it,
and then they wouldn't say it.
Oh, no, I remember all that.
I remember that whole.
Yeah, and I was like, please stop.
And I actually said, please stop.
And it's like, they wouldn't.
And they do it to this day.
But if I beat his biscuit song and make a joke out of it,
then it's like, I'm bad for that, right?
I won't mention the argument is a Jaffa cake, a biscuit, or a cake.
It's not a cookie, biscuits are cookies in England, I know, but it's actually a cookie.
There's a big debate over here. It's a global debate. A Jaffa cake is a sponge base with a jelly orange bit on it with chocolate, and it's not a big deal. It's a cake. It's a Jaffa cake. So it's definitely not a biscuit.
Jaffa cake? Wasn't a biscuit.
It's a Jaffa cake, so that's one of those little monkey-brite kind of things.
I will, I will.
Well, I'm not going to, but yeah, it's probably interesting to look up a Jaffa cake, everybody,
if you want to learn about some English, British culture, and what they call biscuits
there.
They're all Jaffa cake.
It's pretty interesting how we have these little...
Yeah, because it has, because it has a sponge base, it's not a biscuit, but it's, it's not
a real, it's not an actual sponge, is it an actual sea sponge, or is it, no, no, it's
like sponge cake, it's like a sponge, like a victorious, what are you doing, okay.
Can I have can you make me a pineapple upside-down cake for my birthday in January?
What are you gonna carry it by your pants?
You're the are you the P
Aquarius moon. I'm a queries moon first house. Yep. Oh
I'm an aquarium too, by the way
You are I'm a Capricorn in a query and so it's kind of interesting
100% aquarium
Yeah, so you're like, but see my south note is also a query is and so all my like negative qualities are basically
negative a query is qualities, which is like
I just fades into the crowd and sometimes instead of like being out in the front and center like I'm supposed to be like
Because I've my my north known as Leo and we was all about the Sun. It's all about
Identity and spotlight and then I'm like sitting
Or just drunk out of my mind sometimes
What would my moon I guess be I'm I'm in Libra. I'm right in the middle October 11
Uh-huh. I mean, it's like if you can you can type in the back chat
You have to type your place of birth or a general area like the time
You don't know it
It's a kind of a Toronto. Okay. Hold on. I
Think it was like 6 30 in the morning if that matters
Okay, and you can type in the back chat the year
I
Yeah, you're right in the Capricorn, right? You said you were born in October
Wow, I didn't say that. No, I'm born in October. Yeah
I'm talking a thing man thing that is. Oh, right. I
Didn't say I was a Libra
Um, yeah, and my apologies. Um, I said, you're not on a Capricorn. I'm an Aquarian not in Capricorn
Oh, I mean, I mean moon on the side of the side. But anyway, think that is you are a Libra. Yeah
Okay, you're wearing Toronto and um, can you type in the back to your ears? I did
Okay. Okay. I got it. I got it. I'm gonna grab it one second. Toronto. Okay, and then we grab that.
Okay, so okay, so I was born I was born in the year the Toronto Maple Leafs last won the Stanley Cup
So it seems that I'm the curse for 57 years. They haven't won.
Are you canodied by any chance? I am. Yeah
Well, I don't know if you might find my life interesting.
God bless you.
Here we go.
I have, like, one of my Sadian symbols is a maple leaf.
And so then it's been incorporated on the VSI.
So you're from Canada, right?
Toronto, Canada, right?
Yeah.
Okay.
Can I just tell you and remind you,
Canada Audio is not for sale, America.
You've got to consult England first.
Okay, so the thing that is, it will be, okay, you're,
the moon sign will be the Capricorn moon and the, okay Capricorn moon and the, I need to look at it, this is too far away, I need to look at the close one, Capricorn moon and 28 Capricorn, is that ascendant or dependent?
His ascendant is going to be Libra
So he is a Libra Sun and ascendant and so that's very strongly Libra. Yeah
Yeah, let me just take the house is one two three
Okay, so it looks like your uh your moon is in the fourth house of uh the fourth house of the capital firm. So I'll tell you what that means.
Moon, fourth house of the capital firm.
Um, like I said when it comes to an aquarium I'm a hundred percent a perineum of bleach in your old school with moonlight and I'm a hundred percent aquarium.
Cool.
But um, it's just having a good job.
It's a British humor, I don't pick up on British humor sometimes when I'm driving.
Okay, so the thing that it says, it says, the moon in the fourth house is an interesting
placement for those that have it in their natal chart.
It can be an indicator of a deep-rooted need for security, comfort, and stability.
It can also indicate a strong emotional connection with home and family.
The placement can also indicate a strong nurturing side as well as a tendency to be sensitive
Those with the moon and the fourth house often have a strong sense of loyalty and commitment
and can be very protective of those close to them.
And then the moon represents the emotions and things like that, of course.
And so the fourth house is the house of a family and things like that.
I'll read one more thing.
It says...
Hello, Jammery.
This one says the placement of the moon and the fourth house.
Yes.
So what is the year when it comes to an aquarium, right?
What is the start of an Aquarius and the end of Aquarius when it comes to the start?
I think it's like January 20th or January 21st, it's like right around there, I think
maybe the 22nd until February.
When does it end in February, is it?
100% sure because I've already has that
Directly in the middle minutes
Let me look I can look it up. Let me see Aquarius
Hang on before you go. Can I just finish up with mine? I know. Yeah. Yeah, I'm glad I'm sorry. I'm sorry
Yeah, I'm gonna read that description that you gave the site is actually pretty bang on like that's
Pretty much describe me and it's amazing how this stuff is like there's there's something to it
So it says individuals with the Moon in the fourth house and Capricorn are often deeply attached to their family and ancestral roots
Family traditions and values hold great importance to them
And they may have a strong sense of duty responsibility towards our family members
They may strive to create secure and stable home environment and are likely to invest time and effort into building a solid foundation
For themselves and their loved ones
Emotionally these individuals may appear reserved and controlled. They tend to have a practical and pragmatic
approach their feelings, often seeking to channel their emotions in a productive and
constructive manner.
They may be cautious about displaying vulnerability or expressing their sensitive side, preferring
to maintain a composed and self-disciplined-ness.
That's amazing.
I didn't mean to overtake. I I do apologize. Thank you. Go ahead. I just wanted to finish it. That that was a mean
I'll try to get your charts here. I'll try to give you a copy. I'll give you a link to that's your chart, too
It almost sounds like what an aquarium is as well
well aquariums like I think let's see what house are they I think they're
traditionally the capricorn tents and they're like I think they're at the
11th house right and so and it's out of the spirit but um aquariums are very
They're like the aliens of the zodiac for their emotions because they're kind of they're cold and detached with their emotions, too
But they also they're very bad community
Because they're you know, it's the air the air is everywhere. We all breathe the air
So we all have that in common and so it's everybody as opposed to like with the individual
It's actually the very very communistic kind of
Signed to yeah, because it's like about the community. It's about the community over the individual
How dare you use the word communist stuff!
Well, I mean, it's like, what should I say?
We're sharing and sharing not fucking Stalin bullshit to be fucking
Communist Marxist bullshit of a fucking son
That's what it came from me. That's what didn't come from Karl Marx. I mean, it's like
It didn't then it's some other thing than communism I think right. Oh, yeah, you're calling it coming. How dare you give me this website
This website back here
Thing that is here's the website to go to to I got the link that you already put if it's the same
Yeah, this is different. It's a different site that there's the one that I ran your chart on is the other one
It also has free charts and stuff like that
You want to get more into it, but you can see other places you have a lot of placements that will have a big effect
But the moon is a major one. You know the Sun of the moon, but the moon is also, you know
has the sun's light, that's the light on the moon, it's reflecting the sun's light, it's also known as the mother, the moon is the mother, the sun's the father, the earth is like the nurse.
Right, say, how do you think they break umamumamu and 3-1 Atlas interfere with cosmic values at the moment?
Who's Mamu Mamu and what's through those media or asteroids? Whatever that
The outer solar system they have energy. I mean they have energy in them these after me
They get a lot of cosmic radiation things and it's like, but I don't think they ever really get that close
There's a lot of asteroids and things like that. They name some of them after a mythological gods and things like that
But these these are interstellar. They're not from our solar system. That's
Idea. Yeah, the thinking is that they are from a different system. They're not ours. They're not
I think a lot of the earth is from a different system. I think the space is all mixed up with all this space debris and stuff.
It's like we're all kind of alien DNA here. All mixed together I think.
I mean, there were stars in this general area before our sun was born.
By a star dying so stars would have to have died close by for our son to have gotten those medals
Because that creates a black hole right and then the life comes out of black if it's big enough. Yeah, if it's big enough
There's the interesting fact, right? Do you think universes are self-sustaining by vacuuming
up by every star going supernova creating a singularity or a super singularity and they
have to vacuum everything in and it goes where?
Is it another universe, another time, another dimension,
or is it just to create another big fan in the future?
Or does the stuff go that falls into a black hole?
The best that we can say is it just goes into a point at the center,
but that just doesn't make sense, right?
Sorry, fella, I don't mean to be a prick, but a super...
A singularity is a black hole.
That's what I'm saying. That's what I'm saying that at the center of the black hole is the singularity as far as you can say as far as our math goes
It breaks down
So all we can say is that it seems to fall right to the center a center point
Which is the singularity, but that just doesn't make sense as far as the way we understand things, right?
Matter is is something that that you can touch it has a dimension to it
So how does it lose dimension in a black hole?
Well, then the quantum reality comes into it.
But why does stars exist?
Because they have to exist.
The point is that they are born, they die,
they create black holes.
They've become quantum singularities.
They've become super heavy, materialistic, I mean,
because they're stuck in every pulling,
every thinking matter and light in it.
Do you think the universe has so many dice and hoovers that it's self-perpetuating?
Hoovers? I mean, now you have my nurses.
Probably.
Not the galaxy.
You're just very confusing me.
Probably.
As I say, just statistically, chances are it is self-perpetuating. It keeps going.
Whether it it combines again and starts again, or whatever it does. I would say chances are it is
Forever well this this matter and light has to go somewhere when it's soaked in with a gravitational pull like a quantum singularity
It's interesting thing about I'm not really that technical about like I didn't really do that well in science and stuff like that. I do like a
Find some stuff interesting, but the first thing my physics teacher said in our 10th grade a physics class was this is all bullshit
This is all just you know man-made
Theories and ideas to make ourselves feel better like we're explaining something, but they're really not
This idea is not proven
Things are proven to a point, but yeah, I agree with you that you can't say it certainly is with 100%
We can't say that there's still the chance that we are mistaken in something
Right, I mean if you study into a to Tibetan Buddhism, it's really interesting. Well, you know Buddhism in general will have like a lot of
Interesting things that we're really well. This is from a couple thousand years ago
There's like a lot of science in here
But they do talk about the reality of existence being emptiness and like that and that something did come from nothing
Like there like there was nothing and so it created this vacuum and then everything came out of the vacuum or something like that
You know, it's like so
There's interesting ways to think about things, I guess, but think about it
Universe does just continue just like this the way it is right now if it just continues and everything spreads out and it just kind of becomes
It dies eventually
That's so far, we are still at the very very beginning of it all.
There's a breath, it's a breath, it's a breath.
Can I just throw this conversation back to how it started?
Thing that is, understand,
Umamumamu, and now we've got three one-atlas,
interstellar visitors,
that are doing stuff that's unpredictable with it all perceived science and observation.
And don't forget science and observation is science.
But quantum realities, until it's observed, it can be anything.
Oh dear.
Well, yeah, so then it can be fit anything that gives too much of a possibility to even consider it and it kind of like stops
You from thinking about it because it's too much to think about so, you know
It's sometimes better like to like I have a simple explanation on some things
Well, the latest explanation is on 3.1 Atlas is it's nuclear powered. It's driving itself
It's going faster. It's making maneuvers
But we're not going to see it. It's just going to watch us when it passes on the slingshot of gravity
We do keep making discoveries too even though they've slowed down that it's not like it was back in the industrial age
We are still making discoveries that
That could open things up for us, right?
Like I mean right now they're talking that they may have actually discovered an actual monopole
Things that that physics says should not exist. Yeah, I totally agree
But I was talking about three one Atlas itself the bigger very bigger cousin our
Interstellar visitor that's not umamu-mamu. I was talking about
Right. Yeah. Yeah, my favorite. Yeah, just saying as far as us being able to explain things. We're always
Discovering new things right that push it a little bit further. Oh shit
Yeah, which is good. I like that
Well, yeah, I mean it's like that's what
Like you know life is about us like this constant like there's we're not done discovering things and we discovered everything
We're gonna go look for another planet to like you know figure out everything about it
Like we're just very into like having answers for everything, but sometimes
The answers are just maybe delus- our own delusions like to try to explain things
Those are not answers, right?
I don't mean to be too deep, but the answers we've been told recently about these visitors
NASA, including the James Webb's telescope and other devices of such nature, have been
hiding the truth, and this is not the moon landing truth either, because we're going
to find out on October, apparently, what these interstellar visitors are about, like the
What do you mean hiding though that makes it sound like it's there's what I mean come on you're also talking about you're talking about NASA NASA's like
Okay, so NASA comes from the word not like Nahosh, which is like the
Serpent in the Garden of Eden the Nahosh and that he was like a whisperer and a deceiver
And so it's an acronym right now. NASA is an acronym, right? Yeah. Yeah, naturally aeronautics spaces association
But it's like also sounds like a Hebrew word Nahosh. I don't believe it's like there's quids
It also if you look at the NASA the NASA logo there's stakes on it. So
well look at look at the latest version right look at you know what the James
Webb telescope is don't you boys
Yeah, yes, it's like a super powerful telescope bigger than the Hubble telescope, which is also bullshit because
Sitting out at one of the LeBron's points. Well, it works on a very different principle and most of it's to do with infrared and cosmic radiation
Yeah, so the James Webb telescope was pointed we're not going to be told
What's recently been happening with three one Atlas the more recent visitor?
But October is going to be interesting month when it comes astrology or astrological events, but
this information of
alteration of path
non-gravitational pole directional
corrections
speeding up slowing down
NASA's been hiding that for a while
Well, I don't know. It's just it's not certain that that stuff's been happening
It probably hasn't been, it's probably all of us are trying to make a stink that is happening.
But if it is or not, does it really matter for the first place to know?
But if it is or not, does it matter?
It's like they're trying to make a stink that is.
I mean, these things are pretty far out, they're far away from us, and they're relatively
very small.
So for us to actually see them, to sense them, to be able to measure what they're doing
is difficult.
It's amazing that we actually can get some measurements, but it is very difficult.
Are they like water bear size, or are they like, you know, water bear size?
Water bears, water bears.
Relatively, they're not the size of a moon. They're much much smaller than the size of a moon and you're trying to see
Relative it's all relative like Alice the winterland syndrome
We're talking about three one-artless here. Do you know how big three one-artless is and why it's been?
Um hypothesized. It's nuclear powered
It's still a noble wall to the other stuff to the planet. Is it gonna be the next is gonna be like the next Chernobyl?
Don't forget radiation does not make your chin obel fall off
Okay, well, I think Chernobyl was another lie, too
I think because I saw some pictures from Chernobyl. He had the philitima philitima babies. There's like dolphin people
There's like werewolves. There's bigfoot. Yeah, I mean, it's like they have all these like there's mermaids
I was like, okay, though. This looks like you know, like a fairy tale book exploded
You know, I can give you I can give you away from I don't know site that might be going a bit far
I mean the the effects of it were measured before
the Russians even admitted to it. The Swedes were measuring huge clouds of radioactive material in
there. I mean, it's not... Mate, I'm a European. Tell you now, all Europeans were affected by the
I'm sure they were because it was a big thing in like the 80s and like a lot of Russians had his medley
Yeah, I remember when it happened. I remember that I was a kid or younger
Nobody was really in there when it like anything happened because you could not be in there without never mind
The city right
With what's going on
Yeah, Pripyat, but this is not political, right, but don't forget Chernobyl is in Ukraine, right?
Yeah.
In the Ukraine.
And all those Ukrainians that died,
Okay
We're talking about you novel man, so I know I don't want to talk about you. I don't want to talk about you
Stop it stop being so political but all those russians that died from that plant